<Mod
	name="Deep End"
	description="[b]This mod provides a new optional game-mode with multiplying the depth of the standard dungeon to 40000![/b]\n\nThere are seven holy-mountains and the final laboratory And after that.... challenging the lunatically enhanced boss Kolmisilmä!\n\nAll the biomes in this mode are reorganized and sprawled, from THE SKY to THE END!\n\nDon't worry about the game experience issues. The starting point will provide POWERFUL PERKS and WANDS for you!\n\nYou can set custom key to display a simple map. Don't get lost!\n\nATTENTION! If you've planted SUN, please be extra careful when exploring the last level!\n\n[b]Other infos:[/b]\n\n- Most spells now have their respective usage-limitation!\n\n- Tweaked the effects of some spells!\n\n- The Potions generated on the map will be harder to break and contain various strange materials.\n\n- Reactions are also more diverse!\n\n- Redone some perks, and Extra Potion Capacity is back!\n\n- Adjusted the enemies and treasure generation, and some enemies is more powerful now!\n\n- Full Health Regeneration no longer increases your max HP!\n\n- Some spells and perks will now use the the right mouse button as an additional operating key!\n\n- More changes to explore, including more bosses who have been redone! And even... NG-!\n\n- Don't forget to take a look at the Mod Settings in Option!\n\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\nThis mod DOES NOT need to be enabled manually.\n\nPlease select the GAME MODE named 'Deep end' in the 'New Game' option.\n\nIf you want to play this mod as a SWITCHABLE MOD in the 'Mods' option rather than a game mode:\n\n- browse the workshop file [i]Steam/steamapps/workshop/content/881100/3356681136/mod.xml[/i]\n\n- edit the code [i]is_game_mode='1'[/i] as [i]is_game_mode='0'[/i]\n\n- if do so, please enable this mod in A NEW RUN , otherwise errors may occur!\n\nIf you run into any issues, please reach out to me on Discord:\n[spoiler]https://discord.gg/cN3T69yPfP[/spoiler]\n[strike]Although I don't read messages often[/strike]\n\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n[spoiler][b]Fast Travel Room:[/b]\n\nAfter killing the Kolmisilmä, a portal under the bridge will take you to the Fast Travel Room.\nWhere you can tp to challenge most bosses in this game mode and tp back after killing them.\n[/spoiler]\n\n[spoiler][b]Weaknesses And Rewards:[/b]\n\nSuomuhauki is very aggressive, be careful! Plus, you'd better just use projectile damage. And it gives you many useful modifiers, including Light Shot, Mana To Damage, Spells To Power, etc.\n\nKolmisilmä gives you most the key spell you need, including Deadly Heal and Small Teleport Bolt.\n\nYlialkemisti is fear of explosion (you'd better just use explosion damage), and it gives you Touch Immunity. This immunity is important, for Kolmisilmän Sydän shoot disgusting balls contain Instant Deathium.\n\nThe MusicKey Ylialkemisti drops will prevent Sauvojen tuntija from respawning, and the WandStone will prevent you from being disarmed.And Sauvojen tuntija will attempt to eliminate plasma and projectiles that have area damage.\n\nSydän would intermittently double its Hp, so get it done quickly! (The portal will bring you two close together) And it gives you the most critical perk: Saving Grace.\n\nElectricity and Critical Plus can be effective at hurting Kolmisilmän Silmä, even kill it in seconds. If you can't, you can use Destruction which Tapion vasalli gives you to deal with Turvalennokki it calls. And it gives you infinite fly-time, which will help you defeat Sauvojen tuntija.\n\nKolmisilmän Koipi(s) now can hurt you through walls, and can quickly multiply itself up to 16. And it gives you Weakening Curse, which will help you defeat Unohdettu and Mestarien mestari.\n\nYou need at least three EvilEyes to make Unohdettu visible, and the reward for beating Sydän includes three eyes. It gives you Fire Immunity and a buff like Freeze Field, which can reforge to pure Fire Immunity perk. It's fool to run away from it, so you'd better be well prepared before the battle.\n\nTapion vasalli is fear of healing (yeah, Healing Damage can hurt it), and it gives you Polymorph Immunity. But you'd better solve it with just single shot. (use Critical Plus the robot boss gives you)\n\nNothing can stop you now? Mestarien mestari can remove your perks. (like Nullifying Altar, you can pick them up again) The best way to deal with it is to kill it right away, such as using wide-area-and-high-damage attack twice.\n\nLast, if you beat bosses by using Cessation the spell, you might miss out on some rewards that apply directly to the player!\n[/spoiler]\n\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n[spoiler][b]About The Plot:[/b]\n\nHonestly, I haven't decided yet.\nMaybe it's a prequel or a sequel of the normal mode, or generalized parallel worlds....\n\n[i]But why?[/i]\n[/spoiler]\n"
	request_no_api_restrictions="0"
	tags="funny,game modes,gameplay,total conversions">
</Mod>